144hzmonitors.com 2019-01-04

# Privacy Policy

At _144hzmonitors.com_ , the privacy of our visitors is of high importance to us. The privacy policy outlines the types of personal information that is received by us and how it is used.

If you require any more information or have any other questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to [contact us](https://www.144hzmonitors.com/contact/) here.

## Log files

We use **log files from Google Analytics** (it’s common practice) for various purposes, including marketing strategies. The information in the log files includes Internet Protocol (IP) addresses, Internet Service Provider (ISP), browser type, date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user flow throughout the site, and gather demographic and geographical information. These information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable. We only use the log files for ourselves and do not pass on information to any 3rd parties. If you do not like your usage to be tracked, it is possible to [opt out of Google Analytics](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout) and prevent tracking cookies being placed on your computer.

## **Google AdSense and the DoubleClick DART Cookie**

Google, as a third party advertisement vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on this site. The use of DART cookies by Google enables them to serve adverts to visitors that are based on their visits to this website as well as other sites on the internet.

To opt our of the DART cookies you may visit the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following url: [http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html](https://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).  Tracking of users through DART cookie mechanisms are subject to Google’s own privacy policies.

Other Third Party ad servers or ad networks may be also use cookies to track users activities on this website to measure advertisement effectiveness and other reasons that will be provided in their own privacy policies, rappagestv.com has no access or control over these cookies that may be used by third party advertisers.

## Other cookies

In addition to the Google Analytics tracking cookies,  _144hzmonitors.com  _provides link to Amazon products in select posts and guides. We only place them where, in our opinion, it makes sense for the user. These cookies automatically expire after 24 hours, and no personal information is gathered. The purpose of these cookies is to track any purchases you make within the given timeframe, and if so, ensure that we are given a small percentage advertising fee for that product. We have no access to or control over these 3rd party cookies.

All links that start with http://geni.us/ will redirect you to Amazon.com (or .co.uk, .ca, .de, .es, .it, .fr depending on where you live).

You can read more about Amazon’s cookies on their [website](https://www.amazon.com/gp/help/customer/display.html?nodeId=468496).

Our current affiliations are as follows:  
**144hzmonitors.com is a participant in the Amazon Services LLC Associates Program, an affiliate advertising program designed to provide a means for sites to earn advertising fees by advertising and linking to amazon.com**

**Amazon, the Amazon logo, AmazonSupply, and the AmazonSupply logo are trademarks of Amazon.com, Inc. or its affiliates.**

We choose to be affiliated with this company for various reasons, including the range, user trust, prices and user reviews of monitors that our users are interested in. Another important reason is the award-winning customer service and returns policy. It’s a company that many people are familiar with and have great trust in.

We really appreciate any purchases you make via our website as it is a great way to say thank you for the considerable amount of time and effort we spend on it and will encourage further growth of this website. Thank you for your support. You can also contribute in other ways: check our [contribute](https://www.144hzmonitors.com/contribute/) page.
